<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Threads</title>
    <link>https://akarsh-enciphers.github.io/beta-Threads/</link>
    <description>Recent content on  Threads</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020. All rights reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="https://akarsh-enciphers.github.io/beta-Threads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Threads</title>
      <link>https://akarsh-enciphers.github.io/beta-Threads/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akarsh-enciphers.github.io/beta-Threads/about/</guid>
      <description>It’s a NodeJs based application and it has also uses EJS as a frontend development templating engine with bootstrap and a mix of simple HTML, CSS is used to build this web application.
This web application comes up with various web application vulnerabilities just like some real web applications have and these vulnerabilities are the challenges on this web application which need to be solved by its users. So this application acts as a vulnerable web lab where users can have hands-on practice on the different vulnerabilities present in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges</title>
      <link>https://akarsh-enciphers.github.io/beta-Threads/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akarsh-enciphers.github.io/beta-Threads/contact/</guid>
      <description>As we know there are many vulnerabilities present in the Threads web application so to find out and exploit each of these vulnerabilities are the challenges on Threads application. We have categorized the vulnerabilities into 4 parts (low,medium,high,critical) on the basis of how it is going to affect your system.
Note : ( In order to solve the challenges hints are provided with them).
Here is the list of all the challenges according to the severity category to solve and practise:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributors</title>
      <link>https://akarsh-enciphers.github.io/beta-Threads/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akarsh-enciphers.github.io/beta-Threads/contributors/</guid>
      <description>We thank each of the contributors who were somehow realated to this project and gave there best to complete it.
Here is the list of all contributors related to this project
  Abhinav Mishra
  Narendra Kumar Sharma
  Shivam Goyal
  Arpan Pathak
  Akarsh Singh
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solutions</title>
      <link>https://akarsh-enciphers.github.io/beta-Threads/solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akarsh-enciphers.github.io/beta-Threads/solution/</guid>
      <description>In this section we will talk about the solution to all the vulnerabilities present on the Threads application:
Low severity challenges Self-XSS   The self-xss is present in the name field of the profile section.So go to your profile first:   In the name field enter a XSS payload .Like:
  &amp;gt;&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;alert(1)&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; Click on update to update new credentials. After this you will see that the entered XSS payload getting executed on your browser and it will keep getting executed whenever you will visit you profile section through the icon given on home page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Features</title>
      <link>https://akarsh-enciphers.github.io/beta-Threads/new/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akarsh-enciphers.github.io/beta-Threads/new/</guid>
      <description>In this page we will tell you about what&amp;rsquo;s new coming in the next update of the Threads application.
Features which will be added in Threads   A user can follow another user.
  Adding a trending page where we can see what’s trending.
  Creating a hashtag for a post and if that hashtag is used often by many user then it can be seen on the trending page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
